module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Which female soccer player famously took off her shirt in the 1999 Women\'s World Cup?', 
    a: 'Mia Hamm',
    b: 'Kristine Lilly',
    c: 'Hope Solo',
    d: 'Brandi Chastain',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which famous bachelor was recently engaged?', 
    a: 'John Mayer',
    b: 'Prince Harry',
    c: 'George Clooney',
    d: 'Zac Efron',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Goonies character recently appeared in the hit Netflix show Stranger Things?', 
    a: 'Mouth',
    b: 'Mikey',
    c: 'Chunk',
    d: 'Data',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where is Dippin\' Dots (aka the Ice Cream of the future) headquartered?', 
    a: 'South Burlington, VT',
    b: 'Carlsbad, CA',
    c: 'Paducah, KY',
    d: 'Oak Brook, IL',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'In the show The Office, the K in Dwight K. Schrute stands for what?', 
    a: 'Kyle',
    b: 'Karl',
    c: 'Kurt',
    d: 'Klaus',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'At what age did Michael Phelps first qualify for the Olympics?', 
    a: '13',
    b: '15',
    c: '16',
    d: '18',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Sean Carey and Justin Vernon of Bon Iver are both from what small town?', 
    a: 'Eau Claire, WI',
    b: 'White Bear Lake, MN',
    c: 'Star City, IN',
    d: 'Montoursville, PA',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the most googled political candidate of 2016?', 
    a: 'Hillary Clinton',
    b: 'Ted Cruz',
    c: 'Bernie Sanders',
    d: 'Donald Trump',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Of the following words from Harry Potter, which is not in the dictionary?', 
    a: 'Pensieve',
    b: 'Dumbledore',
    c: 'Muggle',
    d: 'Arithmancy',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
  question: 'On the famous album cover Abbey Road, which band member isn\'t wearing shoes?', 
  a: 'John Lennon',
  b: 'Ringo Starr',
  c: 'Paul McCartney',
  d: 'George Harrison',
  answer: 'c'
  },
];